Menu

Menu

Menu

* Solutions

* Resources

**Privacy Policy**
==================

At [NWS](https://www.gapwireless.com/) we are committed to protecting your privacy and support a general policy of openness about how we collect, handle and disclose information or delete our customer and visitor personal data. NWS comply with the privacy legislation in the United States and Canada and does not sell your data.

This privacy policy governs the manner in which [NWS](https://www.gapwireless.com/) collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a “User”) of the nwsnext.com website (“Site”). This privacy policy applies to the site and all products and services offered by [NWS](https://www.gapwireless.com/). The privacy policy does not apply to the practices of third parties that we do not own or control, including but not limited to any third-party websites, services and applications that you elect to access through our websites.

**Personal identification information**

We may collect personal identification information from users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when users visit our site, register on the site, place an order, fill out a form, respond to a survey, and in connection with any other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, mailing address, and phone number. Users may, however, visit our site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain site related activities.

**Non-personal identification information**

We may collect non-personal identification information about users whenever they interact with our site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about users means of connection to our site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

**Web browser cookies**

Our site may use “cookies” to enhance user experience. User’s web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert them when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the site may not function properly.

**How we use collected information**

[NWS](https://www.gapwireless.com/) may collect and use the users personal information for the following purposes:

* To run and operate our site  
    We may need user information to display content on the site correctly.
* To improve customer service  
    The information provided by users helps us respond to customer service requests and support needs more efficiently.
* To personalize user experience  
    We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our users as a group use the services and resources provided on our site.
* To improve our site  
    We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services.
* To process payments  
    We may use the information users provide about themselves when placing an order only to provide service to that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to provide the service.
* To run a promotion, contest, survey, or other site feature  
    To send users information they agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to them.
* To manage product reviews and ratings  
    We may use third party service providers to help us manage product reviews and ratings left by users.
* To send periodic emails  
    We may use the email address to send user information and updates pertaining to their order. The user email address may also be used to respond to their inquiries, questions, and/or other requests.
* To protect our Services. We may process your information as part of our efforts to keep our services safe and secure, including fraud monitoring and prevention.
* To identify usage trends. We may process information about how you use our services to better understand how they are being used so we can improve them.
* To determine the effectiveness of our marketing and promotional campaigns. We may process your information to better understand how to provide marketing and promotional campaigns that are most relevant to your business.

**How we protect your information**

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our site.

**Sharing your personal information**

We do not sell, trade, or rent users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above. We may use third-party service providers to help us operate our business and the site or administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out newsletters, surveys, or any other related information. We may share your information with these third parties for those limited purposes you have given us your permission.

**Electronic newsletters**

If user decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. We may use third party service providers to help us operate our business and the site or administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out newsletters or surveys. We may share your information with these third parties for those limited purposes provided that you have given us your permission.

**Third party websites**

Users may find advertising or other content on our site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our site, is subject to that website’s own terms and policies.

**Advertising**

Ads appearing on our site may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile non personal identification information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

**User content**

[NWS](https://www.gapwireless.com/) provides some opportunities for you to generate your own internet-based content about [NWS](https://www.gapwireless.com/) and our partner products and services. Typically, the personal information that you provide in this user content will be shared outside of NWS as described below.

* User-generated comments  
    The [NWS](https://www.gapwireless.com/) website may contain areas where users can transmit or post communications, for example, on blogs or in user forums. Any personal information you submit there will be publicly available, and can be read, collected, or used by other users, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personal information you choose to submit in such public areas.
* Social media widgets  
    The [NWS](https://www.gapwireless.com/) website may include social media features, such as the Facebook or Twitter Like button, widgets such as the “Share This” button or interactive mini programs that run on our website. These features may collect online usage information through cookies or web beacons. Social media features and widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our website. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy statement of the social media company providing them. Please note that we do not control, and are not responsible for, other uses of your personal information by your third-party social media provider.
* Testimonials  
    [NWS](https://www.gapwireless.com/) sometimes posts on our website customer testimonials that may contain personal information. We obtain our customers’ consent by posting their name or other personal information along with their testimonial prior to posting the testimonial on our website. If you wish to update or delete your testimonial, please contact [NWS](https://www.gapwireless.com/).

**Changes to this privacy policy**

[NWS](https://www.gapwireless.com/) has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. We encourage users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

**Your acceptance of these terms**

By using this site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our site. Your continued use of the site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

**Contacting us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us.

101 W Chapel Hill St  
Suite 210  
Durham, NC 27701

Toll-free: 1-855-826-3781  
Email: info@nwsnext.com

**Review, update or delete the data we collect from you**  
Based on the applicable laws, you may have the right to request access to the personal information we collect from you, change that information, or delete it. To request to review, update, or delete your personal information, please contact us via info@nwsnext.com.

Last updated on May 9, 2023.

Stay Updated with our Newsletter
--------------------------------

Stay Updated with  
Our Newsletter
----------------------------------

Subscribe for latest news on sales, promotions, and new products from NWS

### Stay Updated with our Newsletter

* Enter Your Email\*
    
* Interests\*
    
    * [x]  Fiber & Broadband
    * [x]  Test & Measurement
    * [x]  Telecom Infrastructure
    * [x]  ICT Solutions
    
* Comments
    
    This field is for validation purposes and should be left unchanged.

Established in 2012, NWS is a technology infrastructure solutions provider committed to helping companies of all sizes build the connected world of today and tomorrow. From custom connectivity, kitting, logistics, telecom infrastructure materials, and test and measurement solutions, our goal is to develop and deliver solutions for the world we need next.

#### Menu

Menu

#### Quick Links

Menu

#### Contact Us

#### Follow Us

Copyright ©NWS. All Rights Reserved
